https://www.vocon.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Vocon will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us.
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting the Vocon website. Vocon is committed to protecting your privacy and will collect no personal information about you unless you choose to provide that information to us. Such information is securely stored within the Vocon private network. Some information may also be shared with Vocon business partners and other organizations and individuals with which Vocon has established a strategic alliance or other contractual relationship. The primary purpose behind the sharing of information is to better the services being provided to you by Vocon and by the organizations and individuals for which Vocon has established contractual relationships. Information will also be used to improve Vocon sales, marketing, and business development efforts.
How we handle information about your visit to our site:
If you read or download information, we automatically collect and store:
the requested web page
the domain from which you access the Internet (e.g. att.net)
the date and time you access our site
status of the request (e.g. success or failure)
the type and version of your web browser (Firefox, Explorer, etc.)
the operating system (Windows, Mac, Linux, etc.) of the machine running the web browser
Links & Disclaimer
Our website has links to many other organizations with their permission. Upon leaving the Vocon website, you are subject to the privacy policy of the new site. Vocon is not responsible for the availability of the systems being linked to and these links are provided to you as a service for you to better understand the different business relationships that Vocon has established.
Home
About
Services
Team
Projects
Careers
News & Media
Contact
555 West 5th Street, Floor 35 Los Angeles, CA 90013 323.603.2526
© 2020 Vocon Partners, LLC. All rights reserved. Privacy Policy
